myfreeimplants.com 2016-03-14

# Free Breast Implants, Free Boob Job, Free Plastic Surgery Financing. MyFreeImplants.com

Privacy Policy 

Thank you for visiting MyFreeImplants.com. This Privacy Policy sets forth the online information practices of MyFreeImplants including: 

  * The kinds of information we collect; 
  * The ways in which we use the information that we collect; 
  * The choices you have with regard to the information we collect; and 
  * Our pledge to have reasonable security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information under our control. 

**INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE**  
MyFreeImplants will at times collect personally-identifiable information that you choose to provide to us. 

  1. **Personally-Identifiable Information**
    1. **Email**  
The only personally-identifiable information that we collect is what you voluntarily submit to us. For example, if you e-mail questions or requests for information about MyFreeImplants, its films or its products, we may request your name, mailing address, telephone number and/or e-mail address in order to respond to your inquiries. 

Also, if you submit a resume or application for employment with MyFreeImplants via e-mail, you will be required to include personally-identifiable information so that MyFreeImplants can adequately review your application and contact you. MyFreeImplants may collect and store the information you choose to provide us in order to send you information about MyFreeImplants from time to time. 

    2. **Products and Services Offered By MyFreeImplants or by Third-Party Vendors**  
The MyFreeImplants web site offers software downloads which may require the user to enter personally-identifiable information. This information will be used to process your request. 

MyFreeImplants also may offer links to third party sites, which may offer products or services for sale. Please note that MyFreeImplants does not usually process orders or ship merchandise and that MyFreeImplants does not dictate or supervise the information collection and use policies of any third party vendors. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of any other web sites. We encourage our users to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that they visit for more information on how your information may be collected and used. 

  2. **Information Sharing**  
We may share personally-identifiable information with select third parties, including our agents, affiliates, partners and sponsors. Also, we may disclose personally-identifiable information when required to do so under law or in cooperation with a legal request in connection with any law enforcement investigation or other public safety matter. 

**CHOICE**  
MyFreeImplants provides you with the following choices regarding the use of your information: 

  * You may choose to not provide us with any contact information. However, if you do so, your ability to navigate this site may be impaired. 
  * If you would like to change or modify information you have previously provided us, please contact us. 
  * If you have any questions about this privacy policy or the practices of our web site, please contact us. 

**NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our website so you will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. 

**SECURITY**  
We make every effort to have reasonable security procedures in place to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information under our control. If you have any questions about the security of our web site or about this privacy policy, please contact us. 

**Tabitha**

In today's economy it is almost impossible to get a loan for cosmetic surgery. MyFreeImplants provided me with a no debt solution where I made amazing connections with generous men. Once shy, I am now proud to display my new body for the world to see!
